I reminded Parak of your order
to kill Delgado.
It seems he doesn't want
to do it.
I know he will.
He's never let us down.
Your protection here.
Who's going to kill me?
I am thinking, Diego,
you're the one
who's going to do it.
I might get in danger with that.
Just like what happened
in my car,
where they found a gun.
Only you can do that.
Just remember, I warned you.
Who's paying you now?
Are you a puppet
of the syndicates too?
Thanks for what you did earlier.
Clarissa.
I'm Yvette.
We have upcoming medical
missions at our foundation.
We need more volunteers.
I've retrieved it.
I've approached three experts.
The flash drive
can't really be restored.
What now? How are we going
to help father now?
I just want to solve
our problems
so we can be complete again.
But what are we going to do?
How can you earn
someone's trust?
It's Golda.
You have to earn someone's heart
first so they can trust you.
I'll go outside.
I'll come with you.
Me too!
Get your keys.
Hurry up!
Andrew!
JoeyOnDuty?
What are you doing here?
I need your help.
Help for what?
I need to find Golda.
Joey!
The car is ready.
Let's go!
You know...
You know how girls are.
You know, they take their time.
Sometimes they want
to smell good, look good.
- Maybe she's taking her time.
- It's already night.
It's late.
Where's Joey?
Hey, Joey!
Are you there?
Oh my, I told you before,
didn't I?
Don't look for someone
who's not here.
Don't look for Joey
when I'm here.
Lola, please.
That's enough.
Stop flirting around.
We're looking for Joey.
So noisy.
What's with you?
She's gone!
She left a while ago.
Do you know where she went?
Where?
Maybe she just wants
to leave alone.
Where did Joey go?
What happened?
Why do you suddenly need
my help?
The flash drive
hasn't been restored...
so the video is gone.
I need to talk to Golda.
Trust is based on feelings.
You need to win someone's heart
first so they can trust you.
Well, that's because
your flash drive
looks like it can never be
repaired.
Anyway...
what do you need from Golda?
I want to talk to her
so I can get her to admit
that what happened between her
and father isn't true.
And so she can tell me
who really ordered her
to discredit father like that.
That would help father,
wouldn't it?
Please, Andrew.
If I have to kneel
in front of you, I will.
Please, I'll do anything.
Hey, Joey.
You don't need to do that, okay?
I know where Golda lives.
Clarissa...
Diego.
Diego, look at this.
I'm being offered a job,
and I'm thinking
about taking it. Look.
Clarissa.
Clarissa, there's something
I need to tell you.
What is it?
Did something happen?
What are you going to say?
I'll be gone for a long time.
I'll be assigned to Cebu.
Is that all?
Yes, that's why I'm asking
for your forgiveness
as early as now.
Sorry if I'll be gone during
the time my friend needs me,
if I can't help with his case.
This is for you.
For me?
Hey, Diego,
this is a huge amount.
- I can't take this.
- No, no!
- Take it. Hide it. Use it.
Use it, Clarissa.
You need this
while Miguel is in jail.
This is my payment for the sins
I committed against you.
What are you saying?
Clarissa, I haven't been honest
with your family.
There are also...
There are also many things
I want to tell you face-to-face,
but I can't.
Maybe...
Maybe I'm afraid
of what you might say to me.
But...
Clarissa, believe me.
I just want to let you know
that I did everything
to protect your husband,
even my godchild, Joey...
because you are all important
to me.
You are all so important...
especially you.
Matias, what's the news?
Boss, I don't know if Parak
is being lazy.
He's here at Delgado's house...
but his target is not here.
Parak has his own strategy.
He doesn't need
to be guarded anymore.
What if he doesn't want to do
what you're asking him to do?
Maybe later he's crossing
two rivers.
Parak can't fight the group,
especially me.
He knows better than
to double-cross us.
So don't waste your time on him.
Is that clear?
Yes, Boss.
Go ahead.
Diego,
you're important.
You're important to us.
You know, even if you're
my husband's best friend...
I consider you as a true friend.
So if you have a problem,
I'm right here.
Maybe I can help you.
No, I can do this.
Just promise me that
you'll be careful, okay?
And Joey too, take care of her.
And what I want, Clarissa,
is for you and my best friend
to be happy.
Be a happy family when
he's released from jail, okay?
Is that possible?
Golda's not here.
Joey, let's just go back
when she's back.
Why does it seem like
she's not coming back?
It seems like...
she left in a hurry.
The question is,
where is she going?
I'm just here to ask you
something.
What's your relationship
with Major Miguel Delgado?
This isn't Golda's.
I wonder who owns this.
It seems like there's still
no one here.
It's better if we just
come back tomorrow.
We've been here every night.
Don't complain anymore.
Let's just follow
Parak's orders.
Let's go.
What's that?
It seems like someone
is already there.
I think Golda is there!
Parak is the topnotcher
in his batch.
That's why Delgado
is so impressed with him.
I now know why Parak can't seem
to eliminate Delgado.
Matias, look at this.
They're batchmates.
Hence, they're friends.
That's why even Delgado's
wife knows Parak.
You know, Lisa,
I'm also impressed by Parak.
He's been keeping this secret
from us for so long.
So what?
Are you going to report this
to Berdugo?
Parak's happy days are over.
Have you heard anything?
Nothing.
Hello, Parak?
I just wanted to give you all
a heads-up.
We're aborting our operations.
Do you copy?
Abort.
Copy, Parak.
But why?
Well, our service to Berdugo
is negative.
We'll stop now.
But don't worry,
you'll still receive
your final payment.
Let's go.
Parak said abort the operation.
Are they gone?
They're gone.
Joey, even though we don't have
a clue where Golda went...
well, we do have this.
I think we can still get
some information,
just to find out
who it is from.
Did you hear the name mentioned
earlier?
Parak.
I heard that, too,
when Ramon Orbos died.
I heard that there.
And you really planned
to hide from us?
No, Madam, no!
I really came here to see Parak.
Do you know anything about that?
Do you really want
to know the truth?
Come with me.
Let's go see your father.
Can you still do it?
I told you to rest here
in the car.
No, I can do it.
Coffee.
Thank you.
Sandwich too.
Don't worry.
Visiting hours
are about to start.
It means, we can go in.
Thank you.
For what?
For helping me find Golda.
I really expected
that you'd ignore me.
That's why I was so ready
to kneel in front of you
so you'd agree.
That's nothing.
I wanted to help.
You're really kind, too.
But don't get used to it
because the next time I give you
a sandwich and a coffee,
I might charge you.
Okay.
Peter.
Joey!
Joey, you're really
something else!
You left us so suddenly,
and you're not home yet.
Where are you?
Hey!
Why did you leave without us?
- You know it's dangerous!
- That's right!
You even tricked us
so we can't be with you, right?
You're too much.
Sorry, I have something
to do alone.
You should've brought me
with you.
Well...
Don't worry about her because
as long as she's with me,
she's safe even without you,
guys.
Oh my, you didn't bring us,
but Boss Budol is there?
He's the one who can help me!
And tell Jin Ho,
I didn't bring you because you
were making a lot of noise!
You're both noisy!
Just because of that,
you left us?
You know, I explained it
already.
That's okay. Stop it.
I'm sleepy.
Thank you for coming.
I know you're going through
something.
Andrew told me.
Father, I'm sorry if I'm being
stubborn right now.
I was just looking for a way
for you to be released.
That's why I asked Andrew
to help me find Golda.
Did you talk to her?
Unfortunately, no.
She wasn't at her house
when we went.
But we found this.
I know this.
This is exactly what
that person is using.
Do you know him, Father?
Who is it?
This is the reason why
I wanted you to come here.
Talk to your father,
so he can explain the truth
to you.
Because if it were me,
you definitely
wouldn't believe it.
What's the truth? I'm confused.
Joey...
your Godfather Diego
betrayed us.
He's the protector
of the syndicates...
and he's the one they call
"Parak."
I'm so glad you came.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Your organization is impressive.
I'm sure you've helped a lot.
We try as much as we can.
Thank you for accepting the job.
Ma'am, I should be the one
who should thank you.
Apart from the fact
that I'll be busy,
I have the opportunity
to help others.
Ma'am, is it hard to run
such a big organization?
A bit, but you know,
it's fulfilling and also
I'm not alone,
thanks to my sponsors
and to my family.
That's my husband.
Do you know Boss Budol?
I mean, Boss Idol.
Are you close?
You can say that.
He's my brother.
Your Godfather Diego
betrayed us.
He is the one they call "Parak."
What?
That is impossible. Godfather?
I'm sure.
We were face-to-face.
It came straight from his mouth.
He didn't admit it,
but he couldn't deny the truth.
How could that happen?
Do you know,
he even helped me fix my flash
drive so I could get the video?
Video that wasn't recovered...
right?
So are you saying it's not true
that my flash drive
wasn't fixed?
What I'm saying is,
if he were a part
of the syndicate,
I'm sure he wouldn't want
the video to be released
because that can be taken
against them.
Father,
you know that godfather is like
a second father to me, right?
He can't do that to us.
Godfather can't do that.
What you're saying
is impossible.
That's not true.
Father?
How do you plead?
Not guilty, Your Honor.
We move for the grant of bail.
Are you giving up?
Not now.
I know someone who can help us.
If you have tracked me down,
probably, so have they!
I just want father to be freed.
We know everything,
so just admit it.
Remember the order.
Kill Diego, so surround
the house.
Are you done with Parak?
Looks like he's with someone,
Boss.
Damn it!
Go ahead, I'll take care of it!
It's a great story.
Romance-turned-crime duo.
It's like a drama series.
They make people disappear.
So you're saying
he's really gone?